So now let's go ahead and just practice using Amazon QApps.
So QApps are right here on the left-hand side,
and to create a new app just click here,
and then you need to give instructions to start creating an app.
So we're going to actually use one of these examples.
So for example, we can say, "Hey,
get customer feedback analyzer to parse and analyze customer feedback."
So when you click on this,
this is introducing instructions on how the app should be created.
So it says, "Create an app that provides a high-level summary of customer feedback."
And then there's a file that is given with customer feedback,
and then when the given product categories are high-level summary,
generate an outline and so on.
So here we describe two Amazon QApps, what we want the app to be,
and then we click on "Generate."
So we click on "Generate" right here,
and this is behind the scene creating an app that will be fitting our requirements.
We can always customize the app,
but here, as you can see now,
automatically Amazon QApps did create for us a file,
customer file feedback dropdown.
So we can click here to actually upload a file if you wanted to.
So as you can see now, I have provided a file,
so it's not customer feedback, of course, but it is a file.
And then we need to enter product categories.
So this would be like just data you have.
So product category one, product category two,
et cetera, whatever the names would be.
And then you would click on "Run,"
and this will give you the customer feedback summary
based on these product categories and what was provided.
Now if I try to click on "Run" here,
I don't expect the output to be any good,
because well, my QApp is not meant for this kind of input file, right?
I apologize, but I do not have access to any customer feedback based on this file.
But the cool thing about here is that when we are experimenting,
we can add more cards, so we can have more user inputs,
more file outputs, for example, and more text outputs.
And you can configure everything.
So here, the text output is based on the prompt.
And here, the prompt is outlined here.
So we say, given the customer feedback file,
and then we reference the file that we have right here.
So this is why it's highlighted, and the product categories,
and then we give the product categories here,
generate a high-level summary that outlines highlights and low-lights.
But this can be edited, so you can really just say
based on the file and then add and then customer feedback file,
do, and then product categories.
So you can really just start being very creative with your apps,
and say, "Okay, is it only from approved data sources or as well?"
and a long knowledge.
And you can edit everything, so we're going to discard my changes.
But create some complicated apps, and I'm pretty sure, over time,
AWS is going to add more cards in here.
And then you publish, and you will have created
a library of applications, and this is your Amazon QApp.
So I will publish, sorry, I need to put, "Okay, this is IT, and publish."
And now in my library, I have access to my IT app to analyze the customer feedback.
So this is very handy because this enhances the capability of your company
to create gen AI-based apps on your own data very quickly.
So I hope you liked it, I hope you see the power of Amazon QApps,
and I will see you in the next lecture.